I didn't feel like cooking dinner that night
so we all went out.  Aaru creates a
lot of trouble in the car.  She does
n't even let me drive the car.  Here we all have reached the
hotel.  We were very
confused as to what to eat?  I am
asking Aaru but she is not telling me anything.
So here we all ordered Paneer
Biryani.  Actually, it was made very tasty
and I gave it to Aaru with cartoons on it.
She is watching cartoons because it was very
disturbing.  Glass was being
thrown around a lot.  Aru
's father also ate and I also ate and Aru
is watching cartoons.  That's what I was looking at.
And here we are giving water to Aaru.   She has
not eaten even a bite of food and is just drinking water.
Here I was giving you water to drink, so
drink it again, but I was telling you to eat the food.
So she was shaking her head.  She says
I will not eat.  Then we did the billing and then
we all left.  She was troubling me here too.  She was
playing with the glass again and again.
Then we all are leaving for home.  Since he did
not eat food, we thought of
giving him a banana.  So she will eat the banana.  So I ate a banana
and then I was trying to sleep.  Did
n't sleep.  So here I went to
drink cashew shake and almond shake which has become the
favorite of both of us, mother and daughter.  Meaning it
feels very good.  Gave it to Aaru also.
Look, Aaru is drinking.  I was feeding him food but he did
not eat it.  We all have reached
home and I am
keeping whatever I had brought in the fridge.